what up for us has it in a bit let me
get on the Twitter here it is it is
Skokie Saturday today yo oh I have three
messages on Twitter
hi sir can you teach me how to hack in a
blink this is actually a
that's the person by putting your name
but like hi sir
can you teach me how to hack what is
this crap on hack man I'm the head of
research I do research be reseller of
your product you buy and we'll sell you
we we email support that's how we have
bulk discounts you guys know that right
we have bulk discounts so I have not
social engineer teach you how to hack
EPS well okay guys yeah I'm promoting
them how to research now
inventory we have 2764 Yeon's left this
is how much eons we have if we could
sell them right here on this periscope I
would be blown away by the power of the
comic community the other thing that
we'd like to do on this periscope is you
see this for 9:00 to 3:00 could that get
to 5,000 could you and tell your friends
5,000 okay so I don't know what to talk
about anymore because I'm not a CEO but
I do have some ideas we're gonna talk
about two things today we're gonna talk
one about bubbles and about by the way
you guys know that we are um open
sourcing the maps by the end of the year
maybe maybe yeah hang on hang on hang on
let me just let me just check out
something quick yo Andy you got a map we
could show this go peace do you get time
bring something up in like 20 minutes
all right cool all right so we're gonna
have a map for you guys but later and
that's only if we reach one of our goals
which is either 5,000 slack users or all
27 yon salt and we'll show you guys a
map but here's what we're gonna talk
about today we're gonna talk about balls
so let's erase this board because you
know there's secrets
Arkana AI research right so
let's not but we're here to talk about
bubbles today so let's talk about
bubbles right so you have a mapping
company right that so you have a mapping
company and so you have a lidar company
right these companies are all supposed
to feed into self-driving car companies
right say like fleet operators so you
know you have mapping lidar self-driving
car right but here's the problem with
this kind of stuff where do these people
get money where do the light our
companies and the mapping companies get
money maybe maybe we'll draw the arrow
the way the money to us right so the
arrows represent money so the money goes
from the self-driving car companies to
the mapping and the lidar companies but
the problem is this all of this money
this is the bubble all of this money
comes from VCS right so you have VCS or
in the case of way more Google funding
the self-driving car companies which
then pay out the lidar in the mapping
companies right so the light on the
mapping companies can register large
amounts of sales so they can increase
their evaluation in order to funnel
money back to the VCS right so here's
the problem right over here you have
consumers and consumers in our
neoliberal society is where wealth comes
from but consumers don't buy line our
consumers don't buy maps and aside from
us and Tesla consumers don't buy
self-driving cars so there's no arrow
connecting the consumers to this bowl so
this is a bubble it's just literally
companies passing VC money around um no
the cool thing about this is you have
this thing called fractional reserve
banking and the way fractional reserve
banking works is like this okay and this
is a real thing
the banking system I don't know if you
guys know about it or not but if I'm Bob
and I have $10,000 I deposit $10,000
into my bank account right so Bob
$10,000 into account the bank can
actually lend out my $10,000 up to a
certain amount so let's say it's
actually pretty high I think they
actually have to keep like 10% of cash
reserves on hand so Bob can lend out
9,000 of my $10,000 to you boy Carl
but then Carl can open an account you
know what let me do this in a different
color because this is nine thousand
dollars of debt
right this is nine thousand dollars of
debt Carl can open an account and fund
that account with the nine thousand
dollars do you guys see the problem
what's the total summoning accounts it's
19 thousand dollars but only ten
thousand dollars of real value was put
into the bank I don't know about Carl I
don't think we should marginalize Carl
like that but all I'm saying is this
kind of shit is unsustainable
right this is the self-driving car bomb
consumers are over here now there's this
hypothetical line which will draw on
yellow that talks about ride-sharing but
I don't see ride-sharing ever
well not ever but like in the next ten
years being able to compete will remain
[Music]
so now the bank will write it in yellow
since it's just as fake as the consumers
and the ride-sharing the bank has
$19,000 except they really only got
$10,000 in do you see how this works
it's the exact same scam that's being
perpetuated here vc is invest in a
self-driving car company the
self-driving car company predicts that
there will be demand for 1 million lai
dollars so they put in a
pathetic Elora for 1 million line ours
then the lidar company valuation goes up
then the VCS report back to their of
course you know VCS are just middlemen
they report back to their LPS that they
made a lot of money but they didn't
actually make any money because this is
a closed system if you guys study
physics you know about energy you know
about closed systems right um oh I could
show you guys something crazy today I'm
really tempted to do it you know you
know really no no no no no what I could
do I'm not going to do it um but this is
a cell phone so have we sold any Young's
have we sold any yawns we're 27 come on
come on guys buy heels who's bienniums
do we sell the Aeons see oh it's
refreshing it's refreshing her slack
coming if you tell your friends to get
it no we have 27 left you tell your
friends also to get into our slack tell
everybody join our slack should we post
this on Twitter let's post this on
Twitter you guys can watch me while I
use the computer I also have a pure leaf
tea for the purest leaves of tea what
are we working on well we made new model
we have new model now a new model should
be shipping pretty soon but we have
peoples in our slack you can be you can
still be in the first 5,000 people to
join if you join today and historic
opportunity opportunity and now let's
include the link is it a historic or an
historic slack hamadan a I
all right let's look at my tweet
oh we can look at me on periscope which
I don't even know how that works man
all right but back to bubble economics
Oh Oh Maps Devcon without life Oh Oh
guys what we have something for you
today
no but guys honestly if we don't even
sell money on I'm not showing you the
maps someone's got to go out if
someone's got a buy anymore oh wow oh
wow these maps like hardcore wow that
looks too good I'm not showing it to you
because nobody bought the Aeons or if we
can get five thousand people who are
slapped this is doable you guys the map
is sick but you know we can't do it cuz
cuz no bond Yeon's yet today use your
fur coat is for all right guys but see
the problem here
this line is yellow and will remain
yellow for ten years VC's don't think on
a ten year I thought that the thing you
know when you could see them out VC's
don't think on a ten year time frame so
here's the question that I ask to all of
you guys when will Weibo go out of
business
well way mo let's say die alright like
how much money is Google willing to dump
into way mo for some hypothetical future
profitability that just doesn't make
that much sense so we have women new CEO
around here I'm a CEO anymore I'm George
I've had a research and had a bubble
speculation shit and the new CEO started
making charts of company financials and
I'm amazed by this cuz I never did this
I was a terrible CEO um and it turns out
you can like predict in the future how
much money your company's gonna have now
I wonder who's doing this for whele now
some of these companies are straight-up
scams some of these companies I think
are straight-up scams and then here's
another thing guys here's another thing
about you know you know if you're ever
thinking of starting a company I know I
tell you not to but but here's something
to think about
don't raise a lot of money because if
you end up in a place like Zuke's you're
worth nothing
right think of a house that has a huge
mortgage on it and then the housing
market goes down your house is literally
worth nothing even if you put money into
that mortgage right so when you raise
too much money when you take out to
larger to mortgage your property can
literally go to zero but if you manage
to do everything with little money you
don't come my eyes raised a point 1
million dollars it's pretty easy to make
man that kind of money falls out of
trees
um but yeah back to my point so
here's an interesting thing if there's
no way that money gets into this bubble
by consumers because consumers aren't
buying light our consumers aren't buying
maps oh now you have some new one
awesome new one I can't believe I'm not
gonna name any names of stupid B C's but
someone invested in a simulation company
this is unbelievable
right um and the companies like voyage
you know so boys you know guys no voyage
I'm really gonna call voyage out about
this because voyages let's look at
voyage guys by the way I'll also show
you the maps but someone's gotta buy
Aeons or join our slack oh we got we got
four people in our slack our slack is up
to four nine twelve hundred to nine yeah
okay you guys keep making that go up we
get that up to 5,000 I will show you the
maps but we got to get that up to 5,000
how's are we on sales coming we have a
cool live view here don't we we have
live view live there we go you guys are
quiet today we have one visitor right
now I hope they're buying in a line
because if they buy yards by your yard
today oh I can't show you that well
that's too good that's too good all
right um what did I want to show you oh
yeah voyage okay so another voyage it
was a great Star Trek though so voyage
oh wow they actually got to the first
for all voyage come on
so voyage partners with everybody
they're buying all this crappy
technology from every company where
where do they have press ENTER wow this
is a nice website man well how this cost
a lot of VC money man let's look at
voyage I'm CrunchBase and let's see how
much money there right so boy isn't one
of these companies that makes everybody
happy in the self-driving car world what
operating system is Linux with exponent
so voyage histories don't that's not
that much money actually they've only
raised their only raise that 20 million
dollars okay well can't show you that
that was too much you go see your
community do some cool things I go up on
autonomous safety you know anyone who's
open I'm always happy with uhm but
here's the problem right so voyage gets
ten million dollars here twenty million
dollars here and then partners with
every company and distributes the money
to these other companies but like this
isn't sustainable as long as there's no
dashed line so let me tell you about the
common business model gears come up here
we take money from VCS then we take
money from consumers and then we don't
work with anybody else and then
eventually we take more money from the
consumers than we took from the VCS and
we pay the B C's back you see how that
works why is the Maps page on oh well we
couldn't see maps but guys we got to get
to Oh what are we up to in slack for
three nine two four three nine two guys
you just gotta get in sixty eight more
people you get sixty eight more people
in slack I'll show you guys the maps
someday we'll do a Twitter Twitter or
follow a thon - let's see I was a
terrible CEO yeah of course man yeah
I'll heart that let's heart that that's
true all right
Tesla how's mom how's elan doing man
what I'm telling you though you don't
pay a return percentage to VCS it's all
it's all a scam it's all like I can talk
more really about how the Silicon Valley
scam works
you don't actually ever have to pay the
VC's back technically um the VC is are
kind of like a crack dealer they give
you good terms at the beginning you
build this unsustainable thing and then
they end up getting control of it
this little aduba right so how did you
how to trap
from nothing how does he how does he
lose how does he lose control and it's
because he built something as amazing as
it was and how much it did for the world
it was unsustainable so the VC sink
their claws in they get bored seeds they
get majority shareholder and then wow
that's the end of your company right
I'm sinking to avoid these things but
these things are pretty easy to avoid if
you understand what the scam is these
things may not even care if you
understand what the scam is because the
whole VC business model is predicated on
you know 95% of their investments
failing and then the success of 5% is
what drives the rest of it
so the VCS at , the VC don't 17% of the
company so there's 17 percent
shareholder so another thing for you
guys to know it is to clap there's
preferred stock and common stock so the
VCS have preferred stock and employees
and founders have common stock this is
very common at companies um so what
preferred stock has a few advantages but
one of the great things that actually
helps with the whole preferred stock
scam is your foreign na valuations
so the 409a valuation the evaluation
which you can grant options at is valued
on common stock you know what appalled
that I learned all this crap get in here
join the kulluk why should you you
should I'm get in here join the comment
I slack if you get up to 5,000 I will
show you well I'm looking at comma Maps
right now damn these look pretty good
Wow and parts of it could be better well
but no that's dense pros that's dense
well we can't look at until we get to
5,000 people or we said let's say 70 on
70 owns is a good number that's actually
a feasible thing can we sell 70 OS come
on 5k let's do it let's do a 5k and I
slack I like that number it's a good
number right yo user growth you guys we
have taken 300 we've smashed beyond
that we're trying to get to a thousand
by the end of the year that would be
some crazy shit
eons are $6.99 we used to have midnight
black eons which were eight twenty nine
but midnight black healings are sold out
never to be made again yeah so that's a
true thing radians but okay so
about bubble economics do you see what I
mean if there's no revenue stream from
consumers how all of these companies can
exist in this self-perpetuating business
development loop where they all spend VC
money on each other and that it's like
fractional reserve banking and then like
the VCS can talk about how they have
more value than they started with
without ever creating any value right
you know just like the Bob remember Bob
deposited ten thousand dollars into a
bank account the bank whelmed nine
thousand dollars to car who then
deposited that nine thousand dollars
into account now the bank has 19
thousand dollars when you sum up all of
its accounts but clearly well so is the
bubble going to burst I mean this is an
interesting question
so despite knowing this and despite
everybody knowing this you can't really
say when the bubble is going to burst
right if you could know this you could
make money that depends on what form of
the the efficient market hypothesis you
believe but um yeah yeah yeah yeah well
I'll tell you guys Esther this is
okay this is where we train our models
the new model that's going in the car is
this one here this is this is the
fine-tuning training but look at this
crazy loss negative 3.07 talking to you
perhaps a joke you guys um when google
just wouldn't Google just say you can't
load that snaps are ready yet but no no
if we can get if we can get to five
fifty five thousand users or seventy on
sales but we have no Aeon sells yeah
come on people come on the Saturday is a
rough day for young sales I do like this
number of I do like that up everyone
likes their graphic it was not a sale
was that a sale oh I don't know um been
following your career I don't know the
career that's kind of a lofty way to
describe it a view in self-driving for
the safety of everyone or are you
motivated by you know this is like a
Stalin thing man like Stalin's always
about your motivations right like your
actions don't even matter we just got a
look at you oh we have one visitor right
now look at that one one visitor yeah
visitor Oh visitor all right come visit
our shop shop comma dot ai you can buy
things on it please buy things we love
when you buy things cuz we're a company
that tries to make money you know we're
not like but not like scammed you know
scam just tries to take money from from
other people we try to make money we try
to create value come AI not scam um is
there any accidents with comma not gonna
know them we should there should be some
um it's surprising that there's not oh
oh you know what I will show you guys
something else too that we just thinks
crazy
open about this stuff oh wow well I look
at how much miles were up to there's so
much violence there's so much - that's
crazy
wait but we were looking at something
else okay I don't know where it is right
now but we did some we did some looking
into our data
you guys keep open pilot engaged for
over 50% of the miles it's really good
um that's one of the metrics that we
started tracking we want to go up we
want to increase your engage time on
drives you know we want to drive down
this engagements but we also want to
really well you really want to do we
really want to do with already on and
all future products they're kind of like
eons is make value for you and I said
but I say we we're Reese I'm research ok
so eliminate York so that's the other
thing that we're gonna talk about a
little bit today and then if we can get
our slack up - oh come on people you
gotta joined you gotta join the kama
channel and slack we're up for no I'm
3-3 just 67 more to go we're gonna keep
this scope be going if all 77 of you
you're probably all in slack already if
you all get one friend to join our slack
go on AOL Instant Messenger go on IRC go
on ICQ I don't know what the kids are
using these days but get them into the
commenting I slack it's a big party it's
the most lip party on the Internet
I don't like talking like Logan Paul
anymore that guy's a loser
fuck the KS I fight you're not on slack
go to slack combat AI um me I hate my
friends - I think I don't know that
feels
I know those feels alright let's check
our Twitter notifications I love
checking my Twitter notifications I was
a terrible CEO I liked that alright
Jerry Lewis who's Jerry Lewis is related
to Jerry Seinfeld or Ray Charles the
blind guy I saw some documentary about
that guy would you want my dad's
trucking business start logging my
it's not really alright we'll let me in
on a secret
y'all love when I reveal secrets we got
too much miles training the model is not
trained on all the miles um we have too
much miles
we have 5.6 million miles and that's a
lot of cloud money in order to process
all those miles drop slack and use
discord no no no no no no no no that's a
bad topic that's a bad ought to four
nine three five guys you know what I'm
doing after this scoping I'm getting
pancakes yo listen to the Mac Lethal
song about pancakes wait wait no no this
isn't degenerating into the same
bullshit I do on Twitch
by the way follow me on Twitter switched
off slash Tom Cruise that's Tom Cruise
at 2 0 & 1 3 yes right you'll find it
dude hook it up no no no that shit looks
like some pancakes right
waffles trumping yeah I couldn't do
waffles I could but you'd get one waffle
you get three pancakes okay um what you
want to talk about the research agenda
let's talk about the research agenda
since we are coming I research we hired
someone well he hasn't signed the offer
yet but if he comes on board we're very
very excited that would make comma
research three people so you guys know
us me it's Harold and then it's new guy
and new guy remember the old machine
learning engineer new guy is old machine
learning engineer doesn't work here
anymore
I'm machine learning engineer right now
but new guy is the best machine learning
engineer I know real shit
so we'll talk about our research agenda
oh you have an accident what happened
are you trolling of I always put post
and slack we'd be interested especially
if the system was engaged I'm sure the
way you smirks it couldn't have been
that bad so here's the truth about car
accidents guys so we're at yeah we're
always hiring good engineers we're at
5.6 million miles
humans get into accidents about once
every 100,000 miles so we should
actually have 56 accidents at our data
set yeah guy back then do you know but
like like this is the kind of bullshit
most accidents really aren't bad um and
I think that hundred-thousand only
includes accidents where there are
insurance claims or police reports I
think there's a whole lot of accidents
that are just like you know tiny bumps
and everyone gets out my car my car
alright everything's fine let's go um no
but I don't think those accidents don't
count I don't know what the numbers are
on those but I think it's about every
hundred thousand for like you know
accidents usually would nobody's hurt
it's just like dude you really messed my
car you gotta buy me new headlight right
now Americans really keep their cars
pristine you go to other countries in
the concert like beat up some countries
not all countries at all minta you are
great what happened yo Ronald you watch
ten our twitch slam yeah I don't know
ma'am I did that shit alright so let's
talk about our research agenda
for nine three eight sorry it's hard for
me to read numbers um if everybody could
get just 62 more people into our slack
we will be super happy with you guys you
guys no one's born yet then we gotta we
gotta buy yarns you got a body on fire
yes bye you guys bye yawns yo you know
what you know what told me recently the
Carter five who thought the Carter five
was gonna okay sorry this is twit shit
man this is twin shit we can't do twit
shit all
you know I come on everyone just get 61
more people in here we need more slack
users so we can unlock the slack 5k gold
package and then we will click on this
tab right here that says comma Maps
you've all seen some stuff
all right who's messaging me on slack
sorry you're getting out it no I won't
oh oh yeah of course this is public on
YouTube
I guess you paused it now let's watch
let's watch an accident with open pilot
I hope this insurance paid for it as
long as we keep all the accidents we
have to accidents like that we can all
laugh and be amused tad out at that well
it's clearly not comma issue yeah it's
not like you went reverse slow do I
actually type that fast nice I have a
production team they edit it and post
you know yeah you do everything with
editing these days Saul fakers
these copies are all scripted too you
know we got script writers that's really
like I tell you guys we got hundreds of
employees that come AI most-most script
writers for the periscopes the script
writers wanted to acknowledge themselves
and that's why they put this line in the
script that's too much all right let's
look at how much uses we have do we have
users Oh
41 keep it going keep it going
by the way big shout out to
it is j4x right forget an OPC a IAP this
is a unofficial open pilot community oh
it's loading there we go like you can
check out your car you can see if your
vehicle's supported you see if have a
chrysler pacifica any videos of this one
oh it's hard that I need to sign in and
see videos well you need a bigger box
yeah Prius prime okay let's talk about
our research agenda so you guys know who
knows with the original sin of comma a
is does anyone know when lagging it's
gonna lag but supposed to simulator
lanes lanes are the original set of
comma AI so we want to remove lanes from
the model and you think if you remove
lanes in the model how is it going to
keep driving on the highway um it'll
look fine the problem with lanes is you
have to ground through the flames and
it's unclear what the definition of a
lane is so by using more sophisticated
machine learning techniques we can
remove the necessity to ground truth
lanes in our data set and we can move to
path we really want our models to output
a path of the car and then you can turn
the path into trajectory using MPC so
what's the second sin of Khamenei I I
don't think I've ever talked about the
second sin of comma a I publicly but
they're really pieces of shit and
they've been responsible for god knows
how many deaths you know a few a few
deaths I can think of few auto pilot
deaths the radars so the car radars
are garbage and the reason the car
radars are garbage is because they give
you back objects they don't give you
we're all information and all the
cameras which give you pictures they
give you post-process cars but on the
radar you can't tell the difference
between a car and a manhole cover or a
car a stopped car versus manhole right
and if you remember the so you guys have
seen this at home I mean ours isn't very
good at it at all the when you're coming
up sometime behind a stopped car
sometimes it will stop but sometimes it
won't it's all about whether the vision
fusion triggers so you can look at
things like Tesla autopilot remember if
you remember the truck accident or the
divider accident both the truck and the
divider were very visible to the radar
but they were classified to be more like
manholes than stopped cars you can't
tell the radar doesn't give you any
indication of height so what I want to
do is do away with the radar and do away
with the concept of cars entirely like
right now we have this thing called lead
car but I want it to go away and I
wanted to just be implicit in the day so
the new guy doesn't know yet but these
are gonna be these are gonna be his
bonuses these are gonna be his his his
bonuses if car may I research can
deliver models test those one radar as
far as I know it's a Bosch mr R if he
could deliver this kind of stuff you
know we're all here this is what we're
all here to support because if we can
build models that just output paths and
speeds that shit scales to level four
bros i don't play CDF's anymore
i got it got it got formulaic like she
gets used to be cool and then like it
turned into like chess to Starcraft or
you just have like grind openings I'm
not grinding but there's a great little
main song called on it but this is not
twitch so we're not gonna play it let's
see how much people we got in slack oh
four nine four nine you could do that
you could do that you could do that
let's get 51 more people in this slack
and then we will show you the map we
have to do it in the hour - so we guys I
gotta we got to really accelerate this
we got
25 minutes before I'm leaving to go get
pancakes so we got to get we've got to
get more people in the slack or we got
to sell 70 yawns have we sold who'd buy
neons thing no one's by any aunts today
oh I want Peggy Sue I'm talking about
right I want some real syrup on my
pancakes I'm gonna look at the maps you
guys can watch me while I look at the
maps you know didn't like shkreli do
this on his live streams you put the
headphones in and be like yeah I'm
shkreli I'm listening to the Carter 5
and you're not no Scully shit okay cuz
you sick kamikaze was sick
kill shot then you know you got it this
is something that gives me hope for the
world I listen to revival uh you know
Eminem's like just just angry like DISA
Trump and it's like oh man this guy's
over like this guy's like what he's
trying he's trying to bake the president
he's coming out with a shit album oh my
god he comes out of nowhere with
kamikaze with with with like like
something people can relate to
um and then he did kill shot Eminem
Eminem has blown me away recently
so Eminem gives me hope for doing good
shit when I'm 45 um yeah man I rather be
80 year old me than 20 year old you what
this bro it's taking eons for someone to
buy any yeah no I don't know they don't
sell us mall on the weekends you guys
know what the number-one sales day for
Young says Mondays more people buying
eons on Mondays than any other day what
lies you want you know we'll wrap these
like these are official comedy ice
copies how's life in Silicon Valley
comes shit so kind of I kind of sucks
guy's a vest real shit
oh oh no yo I got something like youth
group from Princeton come and visit me
and they want to hear about
entrepreneurship I would tell them the
truth that's right that's right you'll
tell them the truth
Ben they're full of thieves where was
these to you so we got to remove lanes
and we got to remove lied ours we're not
here to make any kids cry we love the
kids we are here all the kids the
Princeton kids yo man make college kids
they 18 they ain't kids they got to
handle the truth man everyone talks
about the truth like it just sucks it
just sucks like don't start a company
it's not it's not worth it no actually
here's what I'm really gonna say right
I'm gonna get into why they want to do
it right I'm gonna get into why why they
want to start a company and if it's like
some like vague feel good like I want to
make the world better shit that's not
gonna motivate you that's not gonna keep
you motivated to do anything all right
like they talk about how it is but you
know these people all they think they
burn out there it's just it's it's
signaling right and if they're trying to
be an entrepreneur to signal I'm really
gonna talk them out of it but if they
actually know things well then you know
if you know things you know sorry you
know we get to do you know what you're
talking about I really like when people
know things finding people know things
is hard I've been happy I've been I've
been doing research for the last two
weeks and I've been like I've been
thinking of like you know all my all my
old machine learning stuff I learned um
do you need more cameras not really I'm
not sure why you think you do this is
this is a topic that would come up a lot
if you want to change lanes you do but
like lane change is a gimmick
lane change is more of a gimmick than
red lights two stop signs um because
what else should you do if you don't
want to start a company to be honest
like don't go certainly don't go work
for a big company the truth is if you
want to be happy in life um find passive
income streams like it's very easy in
the world today if you're a bit smart to
make enough
money to live you know you're not gonna
be the supportive family you're not
gonna support some like stupid
consumption habit of yours whether it's
like drugs or handbags or you know nice
clothes or anything like that if you
don't have any of those habits you know
inexpensive vices you can easily get a
passive income stream that will support
living don't live in rip-off cities like
San Francisco in New York either like
there's great places especially around
the world where you can live be what
musk I don't think he started SpaceX to
help humanity I think he wants to go to
Mars and I think he found a way to get
other people to pay for it which is
brilliant yeah he wants to go to Mars
he's got quite it's great that's the
classic healing let's go on a dying boy
it's not on impact there's a modernist
you know he wants to die post martyrs
that would die
he doesn't wanna die but like he accepts
the natural lifespan of humans and you
know but she's aspires type of modernist
things like if you think of Elan
fantasies or anything reading one closes
his mind and closes his eyes he thinks
about like a Giga Factory in the middle
of Nevada and sharp corners are improved
in the new model sharp corners are not a
limitation of the current camera really
you can anything the car can do you can
you can see with the current camera
maybe not like a 90 degree turn
but 90 degree turns ro42 go 40 to go
guys we got 20 minutes and 40 to go that
means we need to see to come in every
minute or we're gonna we're gonna cut
the scope e and we're we're we're not
going to show you the maps but if we
manage to get in 40 people by the time
that little counter hits hits one hour
we will show you guys yes we need this
growth we need growth man growth I'm I'm
here um chief shilling officer now and
we need growth love growth
growth fixes all problems ma'am
you can have the most shit as backward
government but if you can show the
people growth
people love fro 6161
oh no the guy says Elon you're gonna
come on that moon trip I think the first
things he thinks is shit the rocket
won't blow up the Japanese guy about
like I'm so grave you know you're so
brave for doing this yeah yeah brave guy
Brad guy and like it's not like it's not
like really brave in the face of like
nature it's not I do like trying to
cross the darin gap I'm like a student
talking about like he wants literally
the guy who has more control than
anybody over to say get that rocket yeah
we should we should do a test
we should not yeah I think we should
test it first before we put the people
in it yeah that sounds like a good idea
whoa I don't want to hear any distance
of the Japanese guy that guy is look BAM
he's not building rockets but think of
what like what's Warren Buffett doing
with his money Bill Gates says these
like vaguely charitable enterprises but
like are more billionaires should be
spending their money on art man we got
some sick art in the world
if I'm ever a billionaire mark my words
mark my words guys if I remember a
billionaire I want you to tell me hey
George remember that time you said you
were gonna spend it on art and I'm gonna
spend it on our cuz that's the only
thing that makes life worth living man
you know it doesn't make life worth
living grinding capital is a Maalik
bullshit
62 words 62 the growth rates right now
we're 2 / 1 / 2 minutes and that's not
high enough to show you guys the maps
you put a motor to turn the wheel yeah
there's a motor on it yeah right I don't
know man things are changing all the old
things I used to say are played out of
rockets alright yeah kind of
I think a lot of technologies are but
yeah so just so you guys know about the
bubble scam does ever know about the
bubble scam
Admiral retro who's in these periscopes
but like you know when friends ask you
when when people ask you like you know
about the self-driving car space unless
the worst is our self-driving cars
they're the biggest they're just the
biggest way motions you've ever seen um
so this was the question I wrote on the
board earlier in the scope II when will
way mode I like when is good luck and be
like well I mean the outlay of cash to
achieve the expansion we want with why
why did joining our slack not work 66
guys we're getting growth we're getting
girls just just just 34 more people or
the major interstates mapped just like
the human genome project mapping is
going to be very nonlinear you know we
don't talk about percentage we talk
about how much good stuff we have the
link is slack comedy I please join our
slack welcome to the slack shilla thon
thon this is worse than a PBS telethon
man I guess this is an expensive
purchase you guys aren't going to
impulse buy it all right guys let's do
something crazy who else to do something
crazy I'm doing this with no authority
who wants to do a $20 coupon on Elance
should we do it 21
$20 coupon should we do it $20 20 off
let's do it let's do it
only for the remainder of this periscope
let's see if we get anybody to do it
create discount go be 20 discount fix
them out $20 apply the specific products
Eon dash cam dev kit and applies once
per order active for today we're gonna
turn this off after the periscope stops
just just guys I'm pasting Lincoln slack
scope e20 scope you two are $50 $50 off
three 250 all right guys let's go crazy
let's go crazy let's go crazy scope e-50
let's do it let's do sculpey 50
let's just go to 50 if I get in trouble
for this then you know promote get
shareable link
let's do Skokie 50 no wait wait wait
wait wait no that's not copy link oh
yeah that's copy 50 $50 off if you buy
it during this scope $50 off that's
right only for this sculpey who's right
now to buy any on change your life I
don't know about that man we're not
gonna show that hard but it is $50 off
if you buy it
during this periscope but I don't think
I don't know man
you know what sells just saw a strong on
Saturdays so getting right now $50 yo
let's go be 50 no wait guys we might
actually do it with slack for 972 we got
to get 28 more people take it you know
we don't take tripped up is anybody
gonna use the $50 off crazyyy on coupon
shit's crazy
we can never lowered the price on eons
before you can get it off $50 off right
now you do it right now we added up the
discount just the discount code is scope
e 50 scope e 50
when and what is the next release so
next release all I know because I work
in research is we're gonna have new
model so we're gonna have new model a
new model is a lot tighter you'll see it
when you'll see what you see it people
on slack know we're going for 5,000
people on slack so what we need we need
27 more people you guys can do it you
got you got ten minutes twenty seven
more people scope e50 get in by your
yarn scope e 50 will this beg ah to
marry you puts it in a new account so
yeah I mean so no like I think you
actually can I think you much she can do
that yeah I think you can I don't know
what the laws are up fractional reserve
banking but yeah yeah let's let's just
give it a Mary - um wait for $50 no it
is $50 guys it is $50 right now if you
buy I don't know this is an experiment
I'm not sure we're gonna get sales we'll
see I don't know who's in here right now
gotta buy it right now
during the scope e but the outstanding
orders are gonna be like I want my $50
off I don't know if we can do that yeah
buy it now Eon is 50 bucks right now 50
bucks off no not $50 right against man
oh okay okay come on come on Sally on
stellar yes sculpey 50 if you use the
code scope e 50 a check out on the
common I website will give you $50 off
the US and it doesn't work with those
you want to buy Eon with 50 bucks no you
can't buy you own with 50 bucks no 50
bitcoins you can buy you if you send me
50 bitcoins
I also need I'll send you my you check
your slack message
wait that's public hey Andy
now we're good okay guys
maps maps aren't public the some naps if
you know where to look I didn't realize
I didn't realize something was public
but uh is there a yes sir we should
hang on let's see
oh no that map doesn't have any of the
data check yo says you're just buying
the yarn did you just buy any on live
right here on the periscope dad be crazy
if you did yo we just sold the yard
what are
that's right we got one order 679
dollars
wait seven people are checking out right
now holy crap
well now this is crazy I've never seen
that number be so big he's gonna sell us
guys man
using this coupon is good well no I
don't know about that no sculpey 50 yeah
get that Gopi 50 right now the website's
not good an iPhone yeah yeah our
designers on vacation okay guys we got
to get 21 more people in here the price
is 649 that's right with scope e 50 got
the craziness discount away little wait
so how much people are checking out
right now wait zero seven seven no it's
50 off it's 50 off I listened to you
Scopus we listen um you do oh you only
have a few more minutes though well I'm
just gonna work I love when we can offer
discounts for you bros I don't know me I
might have to pay this discount
out-of-pocket cause it's not authorized
yeah no that iPhone excess max is pretty
nice though to say and yeah shipping us
30 bucks International International
shipping is 30 bucks that's true um
domestic shipping is free I wouldn't I
wouldn't charge you if I didn't get paid
some countries you have to pay more than
30 bucks to ship any on to international
shipping is scam first 5000 oh man oh
this is close sit with 16 people away
we're 16 people away do we just get we
got six visitors right now
now this is the most exciting this thing
has ever been can trump museum and I
don't know you could try Yanis for
everybody
do you have reps in Santa Monica we
don't have reps anywhere I've got 80
people checking out come on guys convert
be purchasers right now get in the first
5,000 people on slack
this is Skokie's thunder Saloth on yon
Saloth on yeah that's true Trump would
be like what is this shit I've seen
cameras on The Apprentice make better
shit than this you're fired
you'll rep Santa Monica won him
model look at this model model where's
my china models oh oh
all of them sales yo that's crazy
there's craziness one thousand three
hundred fifty eight dollars - it is
crazy
we're gonna keep this selleth ongoing
should we tweet about it now because
then people are gonna complain later
they're gonna be like I wanted the $50
off it's just for people who are
watching this periscope and who are on
our slack right now if you're thinking
about joining the comment 'i'd community
today you get $50 off Oh
moving to the moon 1300 $36 we got three
orders right now look at that crazy
trend line going up
oh we're gonna keep the Skokie going
we're gonna keep the scope ego and you
guys are gonna get to see maps even if
it goes a little past an hour that's we
got 11 more people we got to go we are
live we are live periscope get in to the
periscope join the common community has
never been a better day you can get $50
off Annie on with promo code scope e 50
yo okay
okay we got we got
I'm zero over here we got four nine nine
zero just you remember last self-driving
cars are scams and bubbles let's draw a
merry up on the board here yeah we could
do Mary that's right and now the bank
has crazy amounts of money right
we're really getting into the red here
yeah let's say this is fractional
reserve banking if you guys don't know
what it is looking off you're being
scammed Oh $20 for panty you want $20
off panda okay $20 off panda let's do it
let's do it
Panda 20 panda 20 by your pandas right
now get $20 off panda Panda 20 no just
kidding
10 of the $99 let's bring up a picture
of troll face that's dry
hey we're not lowering the price on
pandas let's not get too crazy here guys
beep Amazon Amazon and all mad okay okay
okay okay okay okay all right I was
offended by something recently and I'll
show you guys what I was offended by we
got a one star review on Panda
P X huge disappointment
worthless patrol face okay wait I'm
actually gonna do that I'm actually
gonna do that can I make a coupon create
discount discount code troll face
in here fixed amount discount value
negative $20 specific products panda
oh my god I think I just heard you guys
the stock numbers on pandas that's crazy
limit to one use per customer
that's right okay you guys know no
discount value must be greater than or
equal to zero it can we do zero
let's do zero oh yes
you can also buy pandas with discount
code trollface let's tweet about that
get zero dollars off comma AI panda with
discount code troll face wait we need a
link there we go Ling now let's get a
picture of troll face save image yep go
yup Twitter tweet downloads troll face
oh yeah
Oh yo I'm allowed to give $0 discount
get panda's all Panda wait it's not $0
today you know it's a zero dog discount
it works on both pandas you can only use
it once per cart though yo guys guys
5000 that's crazy that's crazy I love
you all thank you so much for reaching
5000 thank you for buying for aeons are
people still check it why we got seven
people checking out this is crazy this
is crazy
convert convert convert convert as long
as this keeps going will keep scope e-50
a lot as promised let's take a little
look at the maps over here right so
we've just been working on the bay
we don't have the lanes processed well
yet you can see that we are pretty good
covered to the Bay Area we have full
coverage of all the highways it looks
like it stops right here so you can see
these are all the routes now we don't
have the the stitcher task running right
now
oops but you can see that each one of
these is a frame so every single one of
these little things that you see is a
frame somewhere in our data set so like
let's look at that frame right
we have lanes here as well so let's
let's hide these for now
now unfortunately the lanes are not post
processed right now so this is just with
the gray panda as it purely is but we're
working on the script right now which is
going to merge all of this into one it's
called map zipper but that's where we
have lanes we have lanes on all the
interstates in the Bay Area and
hopefully this will be done by October
first GPS is not being used division D
yet we're going to start using GPS in
0.6 0.6 is probably going to require
gray panda so you can see like look here
we can see like what's this this rotor
look like let's click here and we can
see it load up here for that frame right
this is beautiful let's see if we got
worms
okay we have warp still oh yeah look at
these so these are all the points that
cluster in the comment
let's disable that yeah look at that
look at that 3d map of the world too big
we're suggesting the point size here
not 43 bad no three okay so this is this
is a three-dimensional map of the world
you can see this is a bridge here those
are on ramps and off ramps you can see
the how could it be 3d map with the
earth it's like guys III do have
something I'm sorry to tell you even
though we all know the earth is flat if
you make maps where it's a small
percentage of our Bay Area drives um if
if you make you like the fact that the
stream looks anything but good the truth
about maps is if you make them not flat
if you make sure if you try to make flat
maps you know you they come for you so
unfortunately we had to use the the
traditional round map we are copying
Google with around I know that Google
promotes the round propaganda and we are
on board I'm very sorry about it but our
maps are going to be based on a round
earth I will announce this right now
exclusive leaks but what do you mean the
quality is really bad so we don't have
the stitch you're running yeah the
stitcher is gonna fix a lot of this
right now we're just working on the
infrastructure to get all the routes
processed so we can stitch it like this
just know oh the quality of the
streaming quality is bad I don't know
about that
I know we're sellouts to round arts scam
Oh guys come on come on all right
anything up periscope quality's bad I'm
sorry but about small flat countries
like Holly well we only make maps of
America oh well bad about this all this
moving makes the stream look bad okay
let's make it zoom in oh we can
picture on both like a good map so this
is our map of the Bay Area and the green
is where we're gonna have Lane coverage
why not incorporate GPS and addition
division like people say things like
that where people say things like that
I'm like oh that's a brilliant idea I've
never had that idea before what if I use
the GPS in conjunction with vision yeah
we know as hard
no why have the whole world if it's just
America because it's cheaper to license
map of the whole world and my license I
mean download because you'd have to
write a script to exclude only America
my pandering panned over shit but if you
want to get zero dollars off a panda you
can use discount code 12 pays not funny
it's a part
people people
please go bees I'm not high this morning
I was gonna smoke weed this morning but
I didn't I'm gonna good mood I'm gonna
good mood this morning life's good my
high this morning I didn't have a whole
pure leaf tea and amante earlier where I
played some Jess I woke up I woke up at
like 8:00 this morning I had a Monty and
play chess
today's no it's not girlfriend day today
I'm laying off girlfriend for now I'm
out of that game you gotta focus on you
got to focus on me like why company
buses earth-dog this gate it's I'm happy
about pancakes what have to twitch maybe
we'll do twitch later girlfriend misses
me maybe she's watching Pascoe um she's
not my girlfriend
if she's watching Tasker um how did you
learn electronics and robotics when you
were young I don't even know what that
means man can you use an e on in is that
Brazil Toyota pedals company buses are
dumb today's comma a I'd a
all right guys
are those people who are checking out
right now the dis is about
one more look at the beautiful map
remember that we're gonna try to have
all the interstates done by the end of
the year look at that one no and they
were driving an auto ship go over there
we're not running the zipper right now
but that'll be that'll be fixed so thank
you thank you I'm glad you appreciate
that preview of the maps look at all
this and like you can see like the
bridges down there on the texturing but
yeah that's that's see that's that's GPS
is really bad in the high taxes who is
George Hotz
how can you learn about slam tiling I
don't know gross but I love that people
are liking this on twitter and 5,000
solanki so I'll just I'll just I'll just
leave this last chance I'm about to turn
off the discount code we're about to
drop that discount code not tow face
troll face will stay forever
we love twelve days total face is great
this town but we're commenting I servers
we really we really appreciate all of
you first 5000 khmer i is gonna there's
no memory leaks we fix them all is it as
we yeah khmer i hopefully under the
reign of the new CEO is about to grow
like crazy when I've shown the office
off today I work in this office I work
in research you guys see my chair yeah I
got gaming chair you can game harder and
more Pro with it that's what it's out on
the website glad to show you guys a
little bit of preview of maps and I'm PR
Bros on PR I'm useless as a developer I
can't code man I can't code man
well things are Ricardo here let's get
rid of that discount let's get rid of
that scope e-50 discount two lucky
people got Skokie 50
disable but ice goby 50 whatever the
wider one experiments being done but
check and we're working on making sure
our maps are very precise right now
[Music]
no we're keeping the topes just got
don't worry don't worry we're not we're
not getting rid of the topes discount
let's just tweet about this first
yep love you all
hash tag first 5,000 oh yeah no we got
to say goal reached love you all hashtag
first 5,000 I'm an Instagram thought
that's right goal reach love you
thousand why am i rich can i scammed
people have money that's what you get
rich in this world talk about the new
model okay so here's a model
architecture see these drop outs so we
use a lot of drop out to regularize it
but a new model we remove those dropouts
because we have so much data now that
you don't actually need the dropouts so
I hope you guys enjoyed the P model just
a last minute by Vasco B's